Guide to the Lucy Maynard Salmon Papers, 1818-1992 (bulk 1854-1933)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE — INCOMING
  - Relatives to Lucy Maynard Salmon
    - Salmon, Henry and Rosene [Salmon?], 1901-1905 (Folder 46.53)
    - Salmon, Katherine A. Hathaway (Mrs. Pomeroy L.), 1899; (2 letters) (Folder 5.9)
    - Salmon, Mr. and Mrs. Kirtland, 1904-1926 (Folders 46.22 - 46.27)
    - Salmon, Margaret S. Hubbard (Mrs. Pomeroy ), 26 June 1892, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 5.9)
    - Salmon, Maria Clare Maynard (Mrs. George), [circa 1860]; (1 letter) (Folder 5.9)
    - Salmon, Maynard, 1900-1924 (Folder 46.52)
    - Salmon, Pomeroy Lyman, 1871-1914; (6 letters, 1 postcard, 1 fragment) (Folder 5.6)
    - Salmon, Winifred D., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 5.16)
    - Sloss, Lucy Ella Maynard, 1863-1871; (6 letters, 1 TS) (Folder 5.7)
    - Wells, Amelia H., 1889-1890; (2 letters) (Folder 5.16)
    - B. G. B., 7 Jan 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 5.16)
    - Miscellaneous cards and notes, 1921, undated; (13 items) (Folder 46.36)
  - VC Faculty, Trustees and Administrators to Lucy Maynard Salmon
    - Adams, Ruth, 5 May 1913; (1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Baldwin, James, 1897-1925; (12 letters) (Folder 5.10)
    - Ballintine, Harriet I., 18 Mar 1921; (1 card) (Folder 12.1)
    - Barbour, Violet, 1914-1926, undated; (24 letters) (Folders 5.11 - 5.12)
    - Bawden, H. Heath, 14 July 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Bell, Mary, 1908, 1910-1911; (4 letters) (Folder 12.1)
    - Borden, Fanny, 18 Aug 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Bracq, Jean C., 26 Dec 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Brown, Helen S., 13 May 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Brown, Louise Fargo (with note from Lucy Maynard Salmon in folder 6.1), 1915-1927, undated; (97 letters, 2 postcards) (Folders 6.1 - 6.7)
    - Bruce, James M., 15 Nov 1905; ( 1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Buck, Gertrude, 18 Apr 1900; (2 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Carter, Edna, Marian P. Whitney, Louise Wells, 17 Sep 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Cochran, May B., 16 Mar 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Coffin, [Charles], 20 Nov 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 12.1)
    - Colleagues in History, [1913]; ( 1 card) (Folder 12.1)
    - Davenport, Frances G., 1905-1925, undated; (22 letters) (Folder 6.8)
    - Downer, Henry L., 2 Dec 1926; ( 1 letter) (Folder 12.2)
    - Dimock, George E., 1905, 1911; (2 letters) (Folder 12.2)
    - Drake, Durant, [1916], 1918, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 12.2)
    - Dutcher, E. Olive, [1917]; (1 letter) (Folder 12.2)
    - Dwight, E.H., 30 July 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 12.2)
    - Ellery, Eloise (with letter from C. Mildred Thompson to Eloise Ellery in folder 6.9 and letters from C. Mildred Thompson and Louis P. Sheppard to Lucy Maynard Salmon in 6.12), 1900-1918; (64 letters, 7 correspondence cards) (Folders 6.9 - 6.12)
    - Ellery, Eloise, 1919-1926, undated; (68 letters, 14 correspondence cards, 4 postcards) (Folders 7.1 - 7.5)
    - Elmendorf, Joachim, 13 Mar 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 12.2)
    - Elsworth, Edmond, [1895], 1906; (3 letters) (Folder 12.2)
    - Fishe, C.F., [March 1921]; (1 letter) (Folder 12.2)
    - Furness, Caroline, 16 Apr 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 12.2)
    - Gardener, Julia G., 1906, 1908; (2 letters) (Folder 12.3)
    - Gillespie, Louis P., 1917, undated; (2 letters) (Folder 12.3)
    - Goodrich, Anne Swann (VC 1917) to Dr. Griffani ABOUT Lucy Maynard Salmon, 4 May 1985; (1 letter) (Folder 12.3)
    - Gow, George Coleman, 24 Feb 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 12.3)
    - Gurnen, Herbert R., 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 12.3)
    - Hadley, Helen, 1906; (2 letters) (Folder 12.3)
    - Hamilton, Clemence, 25 May 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 12.3)
    - Harper, [James] Thorne, 1888; (2 letters, 2 transcripts) (Folder 12.3)
    - Hersey, Helene E., 1905- 1906; (4 letters) (Folder 12.3)
    - Ingersoll, Elizabeth L., 1914-1915; (2 letters) (Folder 12.4)
    - Johnson, Burges, 1920-1923, 1926; (7 letters) (Folder 12.4)
    - Jourdan, Marie, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 12.4)
    - Kays, Florence V., 1915-1916, 1918, undated; (6 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 12.4)
    - Koch, Catherine E., 21 May 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 12.4)
    - Lathrop, Edward, 14 Mar 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 12.5)
    - Lossing, Benson J., 1888-1889; (5 letters, 2 transcripts) (Folder 12.5)
    - McCaleb, Ella, 1903-1921; (11 letters) (Folder 7.6)
    - MacColl, Mary, 16 Mar 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 12.5)
    - MacCracken, Henry Noble, 1915-1926; (138 letters, 1 greeting card) (Folders 7.7 - 7.14)
    - MacCracken, Marjorie D., [1918]; (2 letters) (Folder 12.5)
    - Maccurdy, Grace H., 29 Aug 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 12.5)
    - Marks, Elizabeth B., 1915, 1921; (4 letters) (Folder 12.5)
    - Mills, Herbert E., 1896, 1914; (2 letters) (Folder 12.5)
    - Moore, Leverett, 16 May 1893; (1 letter) (Folder 12.5)
    - Nettleton, Annie J., 1889-1890; (2 letters) (Folder 12.6)
    - Nettleton, E., 6 Jan 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 12.6)
    - Nettleton, E. to Irene A. Firth, 5 Jan 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 12.6)
    - Norton, Margaret C., 12 Apr 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 12.6)
    - Palmer, Jean C., [1920]-1921; (2 letters) (Folder 12.6)
    - Pelton, [Henry?], 14 Jan 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 12.6)
    - Polk, George W., 21 Feb 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 12.6)
    - Publer, Rose, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 12.6)
    - Quintard, B., 3 Feb 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 12.6)
    - Reed, Amy, L., 1910-1924, undated; (12 letters, 1 enclosure) (Folder 8.1)
    - Robin, H., [1918]-1919, undated; (7 letters) (Folder 12.6)
    - Robinson, Winifred J., [2 Mar 1914]; (1 letter) (Folder 12.6)
    - Sandison, Helen, 1919, 1926; (2 letters) (Folder 12.7)
    - Saunders, Catherine, 1913, 1915, 1922; (3 letters) (Folder 12.7)
    - Scranton, Henriette I., 11 Mar 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - Schindler, Mathilde, 25 Sep 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - Shallurt, George B., 12 Mar 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - Smith, Theodore Clarke, 1898-1901; (11 letters) (Folder 8.2)
    - Start, Cora, 1890-1927; (19 letters) (Folders 8.3 - 8.4)
    - Stimson, Dorothy, 1917-1922; (13 letters, 2 correspondence cards) (Folder 8.5)
    - Story, Fanny L., 5 Sep 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - Stroebe, Lilian L., undated; (1 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - Strong, Augustus R., 22 Mar 1906; (2 letters) (Folder 12.7)
    - Struck, Henriette, 18 June 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - Swan, Cyrus, 1895-1897; (2 letters) (Folder 47.28)
    - Taylor, James Monroe, 1887-1900; (84 letters, 5 correspondence cards, 1 telegram from LMS) (Folders 8.6 - 8.12)
    - Taylor, James Monroe, 1900-1907; (173 letters, 4 correspondence cards, 3 mimeographs, 3 TS, 2 carbon copies, 2 fragments) (Folders 9.1 - 9.14)
    - Taylor, James Monroe, including one 1909 letter to Laura J. Wylie, 1908-1912; (142 letters, 4 correspondence cards, 4 TS, 1 carbon copy, 3 fragments) (Folders 10.1 - 10.9)
    - Taylor, James Monroe, 1913-1914, undated; (45 letters, 3 correspondence cards) (Folders 11.1 - 11.3)
    - Taylor, Robert E., 1887; (2 letters) (Folder 12.7)
    - Textor, Lucy E. (with 3 letters of recommendation and the Department of History Annual Report for 1918), 1900-1923; (15 letters) (Folder 11.4)
    - Thallon, Ida Carleton, 1906-1925, undated; (35 letters, 1 correspondence card) (Folders 11.5 - 11.6)
    - Thompson, C. Mildred (with photocopy of letter from Louis P. Sheppard), 1917-1924, undated; (28 letters, 1 photocopy) (Folders 11.7 - 11.8)
    - Thompson, Frederick Ferris, 7 Nov 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 47.29)
    - Treadwell, A.L., 26 Sep 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - True, Helen Elizabeth, 28 July 1912; (2 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - Underhill, Adelaide, 1897-1924 (Folders 46.1 - 46.6)
    - Vassar Alumnae Educational Conference, 30 June 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 12.7)
    - Warren, Katharine, 1893-1895, 1899-1900; (7 letters) (Folder 12.8)
    - Whitney, Marian P., 1906, 1912, 1921; (3 letters) (Folder 12.8)
    - Wilcox, Alice, 1899-1902; (8 letters) (Folder 11.9)
    - Wood, Frances A., 1899; (2 letters) (Folder 12.9)
    - Wylie, Laura Johnson, 1890-1922, undated; (15 letters) (Folder 12.9)
    - Yost, Mary, 15 Mar 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 12.9)
    - Conference memoranda re: Lucy Maynard Salmon, 1915-1923, undated; (8 memoranda) (Folder 12.10)
  - VC Students and Alumnae to Lucy Maynard Salmon (See also boxes 45 and 57)
    - Abbot, Helene (VC 1904), 15 Apr 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Acer, Charlotte P., 3 Dec 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Adams, Elizabeth (VC 1926), 1926-[1927]; (4 letters) (Folder 17.1)
    - Affeld, Benelia Bacon (Mrs. Francis O. Affeld Jr.) (VC 1902), 4 Mar [1926?]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Aldridge, Emma Cracraft (VC 1911), 1916-1923; (8 letters) (Folders 13.1 - 13.2)
    - Alvord, Katharine S., 13 Dec [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Amogasu, Nabe, 25 June 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Anderson, Mary, 4 Mar 1909; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Anderson, Mary D. (VC 1889), 1890-1897; (6 letters) (Folder 13.3)
    - Angell, Georgie (VC 1888), undated; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Argo, Margaret Wilson (VC 1917), 24 July 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Applegate, Annie (VC 1891), 13 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 17.1)
    - Banfield, Edith C. (VC 1892) — See also, material on the Mary Ann Collection of Books about Dogs
    - Banfield, Edith C. (VC 1892), 1890-1901; (20 letters) (Folders 13.4 - 13.6)
    - Barck, Dorothy C. (VC 1921), 1921-1925; (10 letters) (Folder 13.7)
    - Barrum, Clara L. (VC 1888), 13 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 17.2)
    - Bartlett, Harriett M. (VC 1918), 1919-1920; (5 letters) (Folder 17.2)
    - Bartow, Virginia (VC 1918), 24 May 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 17.2)
    - Beard, Elizabeth (VC 1897), 27 May 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 17.2)
    - Beckwith, Frances A. (VC 1897), 19 Sep 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 17.2)
    - Beers, Lila E. (VC 1894), 23 Jan 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 17.2)
    - Belcher, Katharine (VC 1898), 1898-1923, undated; (10 letters) (Folder 13.8)
    - [Bemis], Carrie (VC 1888), 15 June 1889; (1 letter) (Folder 17.2)
    - Benedict, Cornelia Golay (VC 1892), [1918]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.2)
    - Berkheimer, Mary L. (VC 1913), 1913-1925; (33 letters) (Folders 13.9 - 13.11)
    - Berle, Beatrice Bishop (VC 1923), 1923-1926; (13 letters, 1 fragment) (Folder 13.12)
    - Bolton, Audrey, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 17.3)
    - Bray, Mary Connell (VC 1912), 1924, 1927; (2 letters) (Folder 17.3)
    - Busch, Kennarda (VC 1914), 1 Mar 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 17.3)
    - Bernd, Florence (VC 1894), 2 June 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 17.3)
    - Beziat, Kate Bradley (VC 1892), 1916-1917; (4 letters) (Folder 17.3)
    - Bond, Marel C., 28 Dec 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 17.3)
    - Boyd, Elizabeth E., 26 Dec 1895; (1 letter) (Folder 17.3)
    - Burchard, Louise (VC 1904), 9 July 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 17.3)
    - Carberry, Elizabeth Dwight (VC 1898), 1894, undated; (2 letters) (Folder 17.4)
    - Carr, Katharine (VC 1890), 9 Sep [1918]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.4)
    - Carrell, Theodora, 1921-1922; (2 letters) (Folder 17.4)
    - Chandler, Ruth (VC 1918), 20 July 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 17.4)
    - Chater, Ellen Dundas, 3 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 17.4)
    - Cheyney, Alice (VC 1909), 1920, 1924; (2 letters) (Folder 17.4)
    - Chesley, Gertrude L. (VC 1896), 21 Nov 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 17.4)
    - Choate, Augusta (VC 1899), [1916]; (3 letters) (Folder 17.4)
    - Clark, Bertha R. (VC 1890), 10 Feb 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 17.4)
    - Clark, Frances Underhill (VC 1891), 22 Sep 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 17.4)
    - Coburn, Julia, [circa 1918]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.5)
    - Connell, Mary, 1917-[1918], 1923; (3 letters) (Folder 17.5)
    - Converce, Sarah (VC 1904), 1 May 1905; (1 letter) (Folder 17.5)
    - Conwell, Mary (VC 1916), 1918, 1923; (2 letters) (Folder 17.5)
    - Cook, Lillian Moore (VC 1896), [1917], [1919]; (3 letters ) (Folder 17.5)
    - LMS to Pres. MacCracken about Cook's letter, 2 Sep 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 17.5)
    - Coonley, Lucerne Ferry (VC 1896), 1921, 1923; (2 letters) (Folder 17.5)
    - Crane, Ruth Fifield (VC 1910), 1915-1916, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 17.6)
    - Crawford, Ruth (VC 1912), 1913, 1915; (3 letters) (Folder 17.6)
    - Crippen, Ruth (VC 1904), 9 Jan [1927]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.6)
    - Cummings, Dora Roberts (VC 1896), 8 Sep 1897; (1 letter in mylar) (Folder 17.6)
    - Cushing, Margot (VC 1914), 1916; (4 letters) (Folder 17.6)
    - Cutler, Amelia MacDonald (VC 1904), 1908-1924; (14 letters) (Folder 13.13)
    - De Lima, Agnes (VC 1908), 8 Sep 1908; (1 letter) (Folder 17.7)
    - Deming, Dorothy (VC 1912), 1915-1916; (2 letters) (Folder 17.7)
    - Dietrich, Ethel Barbara (VC 1913), 10 Nov 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 17.7)
    - Dixon, Evalyn (VC 1921), 1923-1924; (2 letters) (Folder 17.7)
    - Dunn, Olive Edgcomb (VC 1907), 25 Aug [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.7)
    - Eastburn, Sara (VC 1925), 18 Aug 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 17.8)
    - Eastman, Crystal, 1919; (3 letters) (Folder 17.8)
    - Eddy, Martha Henning (VC 1905), 13 May [1926]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.8)
    - Edge, Evelyn, 3 Dec 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 17.8)
    - Edge, Margaret Wadsworth (VC 1918), 4 June 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 17.8)
    - Epler, Helen (VC 1896), 1919; (2 letters) (Folder 17.8)
    - Esty, Rosamond F. (VC 1888), 22 Mar 1898; (1 letter) (Folder 17.8)
    - Etten, Frances (VC 1891), 2 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 17.8)
    - Evarts, Josephine (VC 1924), 24 Dec 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 17.8)
    - Everett, Marion Willard (VC 1914), undated; (2 letters) (Folder 17.9)
    - Ewing, Edith C., 23 May 1903; (1 letter) (Folder 17.9)
    - Ewing, Minnie (VC 1889), 1904, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 17.9)
    - Farrier, Ednah (VC 1916), 1918-1919, [1925]; (3 letters) (Folder 17.10)
    - Fearn, Carol G. (VC 1921), 24 Aug 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 17.10)
    - Ferrell, L. Minna (VC 1889), undated; (1 letter) (Folder 17.10)
    - Ferris, Helen (VC 1912), 1912-1925; (11 letters) (Folder 14.1)
    - Field, Rosamond H., 15 Jan 1890; (1 letter) (Folder 17.10)
    - Fisher, Constance (VC 1920), 1919-1920; (3 letters) (Folder 17.10)
    - Fisher, Hope (VC 1908), 1913, [1926]; (2 letters) (Folder 17.10)
    - Fleming, Rosalind, 10 Jan [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 17.10)
    - Fletcher, Louisa (VC 1911), 28 Aug 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 17.10)
    - Folks, Lalitha, 1914-1915; (2 letters, 1 transcript) (Folder 17.10)
    - Folsom, Mary (VC 1923), 1923-1927; (8 letters, 1 correspondence card) (Folder 14.2)
    - Fore, Valpy Trumble,VC 1911), 1916; (2 letters) (Folder 17.11)
    - Fowle, Priscilla H. (VC 1916), 1918-1919; (2 letters) (Folder 17.11)
    - Fox, Grace E. (VC 1922), [1922], 1924, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 17.11)
    - Frank, Louise Van Anden (VC 1896), 6 Dec 1918; (1 card) (Folder 17.11)
    - Frankel, Margo Kohn (VC 1909), 1921, 1924; (3 letters) (Folder 17.11)
    - Freeman, Corinne Keen, 21 Jan 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 17.11)
    - Fulton, Bertrice S. (VC 1885), 10 Dec 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 17.11)
    - Gallaher, Grace Margaret (VC 1897), 1915-1917; (3 letters) (Folder 18.1)
    - Gallagher, Katharine J. (VC 1909), 1915-1924; (10 letters, 1 correspondence card) (Folder 14.3)
    - Gannett, Mary Ross (VC 1915), 7 Dec 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 18.1)
    - Gardiner, Evelyn Gail (VC 1904), 1904, 1907; (2 letters) (Folder 18.1)
    - Gibbons, Alice N. (VC 1898), 1901, 1925; (2 letters) (Folder 18.1)
    - Gibbs, Mrs. R.L., 22 June 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 18.1)
    - Goddard, Gwenn, 2 Sep 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 18.1)
    - Golay, Cornelia (VC 1892), [26 June 1895]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.1)
    - Golay, Juliette (VC 1894), 1896-1897, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 18.1)
    - Goodman, Eloise, 17 Apr 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 18.2)
    - Goss, Anne, 13 Feb 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 18.2)
    - Grade, Agnes,VC 1894, 17 May 1901; (1 letter) (Folder 18.1)
    - Greene, M. Louise (VC 1891), 1896-1923; (8 letters) (Folder 14.4)
    - Greenumb, Dorothy (VC 1914), 12 May 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 18.2)
    - Greer, Edith (VC 1889), [1896/1898?]-1915; (7 letters) (Folder 18.2)
    - LMS to Alice Spann Griscom (VC 1911), 22 Feb 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 18.2)
    - Hadley, Laura (VC 1920), 17 Nov 1919; (1 letter) (Folder 18.3)
    - Hagerman, Abby Staunton (VC 1913), 24 Dec 1914; (1 card) (Folder 18.3)
    - Hague, Ethel (VC 1889), [13 Feb 1896]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.3)
    - Hall, L.M., 24 Aug 1900; (1 letter) (Folder 18.3)
    - Harrington, Carrie Bemis (VC 1888), 1890-1919; (7 letters) (Folder 18.3)
    - Hart, Fanny (VC 1893), 1898, 1900; (2 letters) (Folder 18.4)
    - Hartridge, Lyn (VC 1892), 1893-1924, undated; (6 letters, 1 card) (Folder 18.4)
    - Hastings, [Elsa?] (Mrs. Harry), 18 Oct [1895]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Hawkins, Mary Chambers (VC 1897), [19 Jan 1906]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Harvey, Katharine Farnam (VC 1914), 9 Aug 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Head, Betty, [19 Apr 1926]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Hill, Mary A., 11 Apr 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Hincks, Sarah (VC 1910), 20 June 1910; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Howard, Angie L. Sanford (VC 1871), 7 Apr 1906; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Howard, Sarah G. (VC 1889, 19 July [1912?]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Howe, Josephine (VC 1915), 29 July 1915; (2 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Hurd, Jessie (VC 1903, 9 Feb [1904]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Hurlbutt, Mary (VC 1912), 7 Feb 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 18.4)
    - Hutchinson, E. Lillian (VC 1912), 1920, [1926]; (2 letters) (Folder 18.4)
    - Ingraham, Margaret (VC 1904), 28 Sep 1904; (1 letter) (Folder 18.5)
    - Jameson, Natalie Trask (VC 1907), [13 Jan 1915]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.5)
    - Jansen, Martha E. (VC 1891), 1906, 1918; (2 letters) (Folder 18.5)
    - Jeffris, Ruth (VC 1916), 28 Jan 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 18.5)
    - Jennings, Catherine (VC 1910), 30 May 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 18.5)
    - Jessup, Faith (VC 1925), [Dec 1925]; (1 card) (Folder 18.5)
    - Johnson, Mary I. (VC 1908), undated; (1 letter) (Folder 18.5)
    - Kendig, Marjorie M. (VC 1915), undated; (3 letters) (Folder 18.6)
    - Kennedy, Anna Clark (VC 1915), 1915-1917; (4 letters) (Folder 18.6)
    - Kenyon, Helen, 24 Sep 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 18.6)
    - King, Lida Shaw, 1900-1901; (3 letters) (Folder 18.6)
    - King, Frances (VC 1890), (2 letters) (Folder 18.6)
    - Kuh, Charlotte Greenbaum (VC 1914), 26 Jan 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 18.6)
    - Lance, Emeline (VC 1902), 1902, undated; (6 letters) (Folder 14.5)
    - Lauder, Estelle (VC 1904), 28 May 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lawrence, Houston, Dorman, Hartridge, Sargent, Ward, Perkins and Gould (VC 1891 and 1892), 29 Jan 1927; (1 telegram) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lawrence, Gladys (VC 1918), undated; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - Leech, Margaret (VC 1915), [1915]-1916; (2 letters) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lewis, Jane (VC 1922), 29 April 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lewis, Hortense W. (VC 1897), 22 Sep 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - Leyenberger, Grace T. (VC 1907), 11 June 1912; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lill, Elizabeth Wilkerson (VC 1898), 1913-1920; (4 letters) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lockhart, L. Marion (VC 1896), 7 June 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lockwood, Helen Drusilla, 17 May 1909; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lockwood, Mary Lamson (VC 1890), 13 Oct 1908; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - Lowrie, Rebecca Lawrence (VC 1913), 1912-1926; (28 letters) (Folder 14.6)
    - Luehrman, Adele (VC 1896), 7 June [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.7)
    - LUCY MAYNARD SALMON to MacArthur, Gertrude (VC 1896), 26 Jan 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - McClutchy, Phebe Briggs (VC 1916), 18 Jan 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - MacColl, Mary (VC 1898), 26 July 1899; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - McClelland, Nancy V. (VC 1897), 2 Jan [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - McClure, Mary (VC 1896), 23 June 1907; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - McConnon, Jeannette (VC Spec 1898), 29 Sep 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - MacDowell, Charlotte Gannett, 7 June 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - McFarland, Edna L. (VC 1914), 1914-1915; (2 letters) (Folder 18.8)
    - McNitt, Esther U. (VC 1909), 8 Dec 1914; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - Madeira, Lucy, 7 July 1917; (1 letter) (Folder 18.8)
    - Magennis, Mary (VC 1922), 1922, undated; (2 letters) (Folder 18.8)
    - Mallon, Hannah Neil (VC 1924), 1922-1923; (4 letters) (Folder 18.9)
    - Mallon, Sophia (VC 1918), 5 Apr 1924; (1 letter) (Folder 18.9)
    - Mann, Isabel R. (VC 1918), 1918, 1925; (3 letters) (Folder 18.9)
    - Mann, Ruth (VC 1919), 1922; (2 letters) (Folder 18.9)
    - Manning, Henrietta Lois (VC 1892), [14 Feb 1897]; (1 letter) (Folder 18.9)
    - Marshall, Elizabeth Arthurs (VC 1894), 1922, [1924], undated; (3 letters, 1 card) (Folder 18.9)
    - Mathews, Jessie Glyde (VC spec 1887-1888), 30 June 1926; (1 letters) (Folder 19.1)
    - Meigs, Dorothy E. (VC 1914), 1916-1926; (11 letters) (Folder 14.7)
    - Meyers, Marion R. (VC 1910), 4 Feb 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Miller, Antha L. Knowlton (VC 1890), 10 Feb 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Miller, Lucia Wood (VC 1892), 26 May 1923; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Milne, Mark H. concerning Milne Almar (VC 1896), 17 Apr 1925; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Mineah, Mary A. (VC 1870), 28 Oct 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Moffett, Edna V. (VC 1897), 1921-1923; (7 letters) (Folder 14.8)
    - Montgomery, Priscilla B. (VC 1877), 7 July 1918; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Moore, Anne (VC 1896), 1916, 1921; (3 letters) (Folder 19.1)
    - Moriarty, Laura (VC 1900), 1901-1902; (2 letters) (Folder 19.1)
    - Moriarty, Laura A. (VC 1900), 1901-1906, undated; (9 letters) (Folder 14.9)
    - Morrison, Pheobe (VC 1924), 1922, 1924; (2 letters) (Folder 19.1)
    - Morey, Jeanette, (VC Spec 1897-1898), 1901-1903; (3 letters) (Folder 19.1)
    - Murdoch, Jane Robb (VC 1898), 27 Oct [1897]; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Myers, Beatrice De Lima (VC 1908), 29 Mar 1926; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Myers, Ruth Crowell (VC 1907), 21 Mar 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 19.1)
    - Nash, Ruth S. (VC 1915), 24 July 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 19.2)
    - Nies, Abby Ware (VC 1899), 1906, undated; (2 letters) (Folder 19.2)
    - Norse, Mary Pemberton (VC 1914), 1913-1916; (5 letters) (Folder 14.10)
    - Orvis, Gertrude Swift (VC 1910), 15 Oct [1900]; (1 letter) (Folder 19.2)
    - Orvis, Julia Swift (VC 1895), 1895-1906; (8 letters) (Folder 14.11)
    - Osbourne, Elise (VC 1910), 4 Mar 1920; (1 letter) (Folder 19.2)
    - Owens, Anna (VC 1892), 27 Jan 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 19.2)
    - Parker, Ruth Louis (VC 1901), 22 Jan 1916; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Peck, Mary Gray (VC 1926), 29 Mar [1926]; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Phillips, Dorothy S. (VC 1914), 27 Aug 1922; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Pierce, Katharine U. (VC 1897), 27 July 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Plimpton, Harriet (VC 1914), 21 Feb 1915; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Poppenheim, Mary B. (VC 1888), 12 Feb 1897; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Pratt, Mary Armour (VC 1905), [1904], 1915, 1917; (4 letters) (Folder 19.3)
    - Prentiss, Adella (VC 1890), 26 Jan 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Prescott, Helen Sarah (VC 1915), undated; (1 card) (Folder 19.3)
    - Pressy, Luella Cole (VC 1916), 1 Nov 1921; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Pringle, Katharine Hall (VC 1891), 16 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 19.3)
    - Putnam, Elizabeth Whitney (VC 1917), 1923; (2 letters) (Folder 19.3)
    - Quinn, Eleanor (VC 1891), 8 Feb 1896; (1 letter) (Folder 19.4)
    - Ransom, Marion (VC 1888), 1917, undated; (3 letters) (Folder 19.4)
    - Rickert, Edith (VC 1891), 1896-1924; (60 letters, 1 TS, 1 enclosure) (Folders 15.1 - 15.5)